[
  {
    "id":1,
    "question":"Which of the following is a server-side Java Script object?",
    "a":"Function",
    "b":"FileUpload",
    "c":"JSON",
    "d":"File",
    "e":"Date",
    "answer":"d"
  },
  {
    "id":2,
    "question":"How does Java Script store dates in objects of Date type?",
    "a":"1st, 1900",
    "b":"January 1st, 1970",
    "c":"12/01/1970",
    "d":"Ash",
    "e":"1970/12/01",
    "answer":"c"
  },
  {
    "id":3,
    "question":"Which of the following is the tainted property of a window object in Java Script?",
    "a":"Pathname",
    "b":"Protocol",
    "c":"Defaultstatus",
    "d":"Host",
    "e":"Window",
    "answer":"c"
  },
  {
    "id":4,
    "question":"Which attribute needs to be changed to make elements invisible?",
    "a":"visibility",
    "b":"visible",
    "c":"invisibility",
    "d":"invisilible",
    "e":"hidden",
    "answer":"b"
  },
  {
    "id":5,
    "question":"What language defines the behavior of a web page?",
    "a":"HTML",
    "b":"CSS",
    "c":"XML",
    "d":"JavaScript",
    "e":"Super Mario",
    "answer":"d"
  },
  {
    "id":6,
    "question":"Which of the following is a server-side Java Script object?",
    "a":"Function",
    "b":"FileUpload",
    "c":"JSON",
    "d":"File",
    "e":"Date",
    "answer":"d"
  },
  {
    "id":7,
    "question":"How does Java Script store dates in objects of Date type?",
    "a":"1st, 1900",
    "b":"January 1st, 1970",
    "c":"January 1st, 1970",
    "d":"January 1st, 1970",
    "e":"Ash",
    "answer":"c"
  },
  {
    "id":8,
    "question":"Which of the following is the tainted property of a window object in Java Script?",
    "a":"Pathname",
    "b":"Protocol",
    "c":"Defaultstatus",
    "d":"Host",
    "e":"Window",
    "answer":"c"
  },
  {
    "id":9,
    "question":"Which attribute needs to be changed to make elements invisible?",
    "a":"visibility",
    "b":"visible",
    "c":"invisibility",
    "d":"invisilible",
    "e":"hidden",
    "answer":"b"
  },
  {
    "id":10,
    "question":"What language defines the behavior of a web page?",
    "a":"HTML",
    "b":"CSS",
    "c":"XML",
    "d":"JavaScript",
    "e":"Super Mario",
    "answer":"d"
  },
  {
    "id":11,
    "question":"Which of the following is a server-side Java Script object?",
    "a":"Function",
    "b":"FileUpload",
    "c":"JSON",
    "d":"File",
    "e":"Date",
    "answer":"d"
  },
  {
    "id":12,
    "question":"How does Java Script store dates in objects of Date type?",
    "a":"1st, 1900",
    "b":"January 1st, 1970",
    "c":"January 1st, 1970",
    "d":"January 1st, 1970",
    "e":"Ash",
    "answer":"c"
  },
  {
    "id":13,
    "question":"Which of the following is the tainted property of a window object in Java Script?",
    "a":"Pathname",
    "b":"Protocol",
    "c":"Defaultstatus",
    "d":"Host",
    "e":"Window",
    "answer":"c"
  },
  {
    "id":14,
    "question":"Which attribute needs to be changed to make elements invisible?",
    "a":"visibility",
    "b":"visible",
    "c":"invisibility",
    "d":"invisilible",
    "e":"hidden",
    "answer":"b"
  },
  {
    "id":15,
    "question":"What language defines the behavior of a web page?",
    "a":"HTML",
    "b":"CSS",
    "c":"XML",
    "d":"JavaScript",
    "e":"Super Mario",
    "answer":"d"
  },
  {
    "id":16,
    "question":"Which of the following is a server-side Java Script object?",
    "a":"Function",
    "b":"FileUpload",
    "c":"JSON",
    "d":"File",
    "e":"Date",
    "answer":"d"
  },
  {
    "id":17,
    "question":"How does Java Script store dates in objects of Date type?",
    "a":"1st, 1900",
    "b":"January 1st, 1970",
    "c":"January 1st, 1970",
    "d":"January 1st, 1970",
    "e":"Ash",
    "answer":"c"
  },
  {
    "id":18,
    "question":"Which of the following is the tainted property of a window object in Java Script?",
    "a":"Pathname",
    "b":"Protocol",
    "c":"Defaultstatus",
    "d":"Host",
    "e":"Window",
    "answer":"c"
  },
  {
    "id":19,
    "question":"Which attribute needs to be changed to make elements invisible?",
    "a":"visibility",
    "b":"visible",
    "c":"invisibility",
    "d":"invisilible",
    "e":"hidden",
    "answer":"b"
  },
  {
    "id":20,
    "question":"What language defines the behavior of a web page?",
    "a":"HTML",
    "b":"CSS",
    "c":"XML",
    "d":"JavaScript",
    "e":"Super Mario",
    "answer":"d"
  }
]